mainline.com.au 2007-09-11

# Pages

****

**Privacy Policy of Mainline Security Products Pty Ltd  
** Mainline Security Products Pty Ltd has prepared this privacy statement in order to demonstrate the company's firm commitment to our site visitors privacy. The following discloses the information gathering and information collecting practices for the Mainline web site at [www.mainline.com.au](http://www.mainline.com.au/). Visitors to the Mainline Security Products Pty Ltd website can browse the general areas of this site without the need to disclose their personal information. There is also a private area that requires registration and the provision of personal information.

**Who is Mainline Electronics Australia?**  
Mainline Electronics Australia Pty Ltd (Mainline) is a wholesaler of security system equipment. The purpose of the Mainline web site is to provide product and technical information on our range.

**How do we operate?  
** Mainline's stores are in Victoria and Queensland, Australia. Mainline products are also exported to various parts of the world.

Request for additional information Visitors can browse our web site with out the need to provide us with your personal information. In the event that additional product information is required or the password to the secured part of our web site is requested. We request that the applicant provides us with the relevant business related details like, applicants name, company name, address, phone number and email address, so that we can respond to your inquiry.

**Personal information collected**  
All personal information collected from individuals as result of our business operation will be protected as essential part of the relationship we wish to establish with our clients. We collect personal information for the purposes of providing access to the relevant product information that is selected by the visitor. The company will only disclose this information in accordance with the provisions of the Privacy Act and the National Privacy Principles. We will not collect or solicit personal information via this site which would be unlawful, unnecessary or unrelated to the functions or activities of the company. Personal information up-dates  
We take reasonable steps to ensure that your personal information is accurate, complete and up-to-date whenever collect or use it. In the event that the information we hold on you is out of date or in-accurate, please contact our office for any changes that may be need to be changed so we can take necessary steps to amend this information, or take the necessary steps for the alternative action.

**Right of access by individual**  
Any individual has the right to request access at any time to the personal information that the company holds about the person or the Company. This access will be refused where the company cannot be satisfied as to the identity of the person requesting that access.

**Email details  
** The email address will only be used for the purpose the individual visitor provides it. The email address is used to grant the visitor the password to access the secure part of our web site. This email address will not be disclosed to any other party, unless the individual requests it. The email address may also be used for sending you our latest product information, or information on the specific product requested. Mainline will only record email addresses if the visitor sends us a message, or if it is given verbally, phone or fax. This email will not be used for our mailing list unless the individual requests that this is done.

**Copyright and Trade Marks  
** All materials on this web site are the copyright of Mainline Security Products Pty Ltd. All rights reserved. The web site may be retrieved and downloaded solely for personal use. No materials may otherwise be copied, modified, published, broadcast or otherwise distributed without the prior written permission from Mainline Security Products Pty Ltd.

**Links**  
Links to other web sites are provided by Mainline in good faith and for information only. Mainline disclaims any responsibility to the materials contained in any web site linked to this site.

**Change of our Privacy Statement  
** We may amend this privacy statement as required by law, or when our business requirements have changed. Details of any changes can be accessed on our web site at any time.

How can we be contacted?  
c/o: The Privacy Officer  
Mainline Security Products Pty Ltd  
221 Nepean Hwy  
Gardenvale, Victoria 3185  
Phone: +61 3 9596 6688  
Fax: +61 3 9596 6138
